<paper title="全新版第二版综合B3U1-D" identifier="e1fea2ab-914a-4b57-a442-0d883e8bba39" bankid="1" policy="" level="" freeNavigation="true"><group duration="840" navigationMode="linear"><part title="Listening Comprehension"><section title="Section A" type=""><prompt><sound duration="4" src="Begin.mp3" /><sound duration="3" src="Section A.mp3" /><text type="direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; In this section, you will hear ten statements. Numbers 1 to 6 are based on Text A while the rest are based on Text B. Each statement will be read &lt;b&gt;ONLY ONCE&lt;/b&gt;. Listen carefully and decide whether each statement is true or false.</text><text type="p_direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions:&lt;/b&gt; In this section, you will hear ten statements. Numbers 1 to 6 are based on Text A while the rest are based on Text B. Each statement will be read &lt;b&gt;ONLY ONCE&lt;/b&gt;. Listen carefully and decide whether each statement is true or false.</text><sound duration="24" src="torf.mp3" /></prompt><assessmentItem identifier="16E15AFE733C42AEAC6302653AE7AE01" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="12" src="eb82fb2431754264a476af538387445a.mp3"><transcript>The Doherties find contentment with life on the farm because they rely a lot on their own efforts to produce food and what they need for everyday life.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="CEB51F8314224EE6AD71B2DC96A87FCD" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="10" src="d280cbb7e41142b190eb65f81c4de6e2.mp3"><transcript>For the Doherties, their enjoyment on the farm is based on their hard work on all the crops and livestock.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="5C523958CD2142C99E998C533569FC83" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="10" src="c758a16466724c2a81fe0cf22035716b.mp3"><transcript>Mr. Doherty doesn’t make enough money now to maintain their living standard in the past so their life is seriously affected.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="8314C0DBB7A149AABD8A364A89BAB1B9" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="11" src="2078bfe9eec84ad6a8f472abcb31c7e2.mp3"><transcript>Beyond the first $500 bills, they still need to pay 20% of what they spend on medical cares.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="1A7763341E5B4FF284AA6AF46680AB4B" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="7" src="f995bac7931d4727bf405332e197c83c.mp3"><transcript>Living on the farm means the tolerance for solitude and the willingness for hard work.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="4CFFE66C6D65460680771779412568B3" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="11" src="1af08f54d1b847e8a8b24dfdda13eb60.mp3"><transcript>Once economic conditions improve, the Doherties will sell the farm for more than double of their investment to make a lot of money.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="84B01AAC5B9E4807AB68FCB50EB77B0E" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="11" src="3504a901962149188c20584d2a5439bc.mp3"><transcript>In the old traditional American family, wife might stay home to make dinner and the whole family relies on the husband’s pay check.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="4FDB777F68DE452DB6CC1D6EBDCB8CDC" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="8" src="4a453496bf4441a4bda6a63e625c31da.mp3"><transcript>The style of American meals has changed from “home-style” meals to prepared foods.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="F36B4037D3FF48D0BBEC70E07BEB0799" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="7" src="e56e6580b1e3430ea335b63ddb7d0271.mp3"><transcript>One essential part of family that is missing in their entertainment style is togetherness.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="603D97D17FFF42DEB4E0F9BF95F09AF7" baseType="listeningChoice" type="listeningTorF" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="false" weight="1.00"><prompt><sound duration="6" src="50168d7938754149b922cd4fd077c111.mp3"><transcript>The author is suggesting we go back to the 1950s.</transcript></sound></prompt><choice><option id="1">T</option><option id="2">F</option></choice><pause duration="15" /></question></assessmentItem></section><section title="Section B" type=""><prompt><sound duration="3" src="Section B.mp3" /><text type="direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.

&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;You can press "Tab" or "Enter" to go to the next blank directly. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;</text><text type="p_direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks with the exact words you have just heard. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.</text><sound duration="33" src="SpotDictation.mp3" /></prompt><assessmentItem identifier="5B0B5985C8C04A8A9A8C71D7D5218C29" baseType="listeningCloze" type="spotDictation" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><prompt><text>        Stress is the "wear and tear" our bodies experience, as we <tag type="text" /> to our changing environment. As a <tag type="text" /> influence, stress can help us take action. As a <tag type="text" /> influence, it can lead to health problems such as headache, insomnia, ulcers, high blood pressure and heart disease.
        Our goal is not to eliminate stress but to learn how to <tag type="text" /> it and how to use it to help us. <tag type="text" /> stress may make us feel bored; on the other hand, <tag type="text" /> stress may make us feel tied up in knots. What we need to do is to find the <tag type="text" /> level of stress which will <tag type="text" /> overwhelm us.
        There is no single level of stress that is optimal for all people. What is distressing to one may be a joy to another. Moreover, our <tag type="text" /> and the amount which we can tolerate changes with our ages.
        It has been revealed that most illness is related to unrelieved stress. Being aware of stress and its effect on our lives can help reduce its harmful effects. There are many sources of stress, and there are many possibilities for its management. Here are three principles as to how to manage stress:
1.	Become aware of your stressor and your emotional and physical reactions.
2.	Recognize what you can change.
3.	<tag type="text" /> of your emotional reactions to stress.</text><sound duration="359" src="a0ecd73f25c2436e9aec6974a1fbaa80.mp3"><transcript>        Stress is the "wear and tear" our bodies experience, as we &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;adjust&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; to our changing environment. As a &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;positive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; influence, stress can help us take action. As a &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;negative&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; influence, it can lead to health problems such as headache, insomnia, ulcers, high blood pressure and heart disease.
        Our goal is not to eliminate stress but to learn how to &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;manage&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; it and how to use it to help us. &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Insufficient&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; stress may make us feel bored; on the other hand, &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;excessive&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; stress may make us feel tied up in knots. What we need to do is to find the &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;optimal&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; level of stress which will &lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;motivate but not&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; overwhelm us.        
        There is no single level of stress that is optimal for all people. What is distressing to one may be a joy to another. Moreover, our &lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;personal stress requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; and the amount which we can tolerate changes with our ages.
        It has been revealed that most illness is related to unrelieved stress. Being aware of stress and its effect on our lives can help reduce its harmful effects. There are many sources of stress, and there are many possibilities for its management. Here are three principles as to how to manage stress:
1.	Become aware of your stressor and your emotional and physical reactions.
2.	Recognize what you can change.
3.	&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reduce the intensity&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt; of your emotional reactions to stress.</transcript></sound><pause duration="120" /></prompt><question type="text" length="6" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="8" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="8" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="6" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="12" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="9" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="7" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="17" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="28" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question><question type="text" length="20" strict="true" weight="2.00"><tip /></question></assessmentItem><prompt><sound duration="4" src="end.mp3" /><pause duration="54" /></prompt></section></part></group><group duration="1500" navigationMode="nonlinear"><part title="Reading Comprehension"><section title="Section A" type=""><prompt><text type="direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;In this section, there is a passage with several blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank beside the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. &lt;b&gt;You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once&lt;/b&gt;.
        
Drag the word into the blank where you want to place it. If you change your mind, just drag the new word there. The former one will go back to the word bank accordingly. You can also click the "restore" icon beside the word in the bank to cancel your operation.

</text><text type="p_direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;In this section, there is a passage with several blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank following the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. &lt;b&gt;You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once&lt;/b&gt;.
</text></prompt><assessmentItem identifier="B2698AE99E0E47749754789946A79D48" baseType="bankedCloze" type="bankedCloze" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><prompt>        There are two things I have always wanted to do — write and live on a farm. Today I’m doing both. I am not in E. B. White’s class as a writer or in my neighbors’ league as a farmer, but I’m getting by. And after years of <tag type="choice" /> with city and suburban living, my wife Sandy and I have finally found <tag type="choice" /> here in the country.
        It’s a <tag type="choice" /> sort of life. We grow nearly all of our fruits and vegetables. Our hens keep us in eggs, with several dozen left over to sell each week. Our bees provide us with honey, and we cut enough wood to just about <tag type="choice" /> it _____ the heating season.
        It’s a <tag type="choice" /> life too. In the summer we canoe on the river, go picnicking in the woods and take long bicycle rides. In the winter we ski and <tag type="choice" />. We get excited about sunsets. We love the <tag type="choice" /> of the earth warming and the sound of cattle lowing. We watch for hawks in the sky and deer in the cornfields.
        But the good life can get pretty tough. Three months ago when it was 30 below, we spent two <tag type="choice" /> days hauling firewood up the river on a sled. Three months from now, it will be 95 above and we will be <tag type="choice" /> corn, weeding strawberries and killing chickens. Recently, Sandy and I had to retile the back roof. Soon Jim, 16 and Emily, 13, the youngest of our four children, will help me make some long-overdue improvements on the outdoor toilet that <tag type="choice" /> our indoor plumbing when we are working outside. Later this month, we’ll spray the orchard, paint the barn, plant the garden and clean the hen house before the new chicks arrive.</prompt><choice><option id="1">self-reliant</option><option id="2">frustration</option><option id="3">contentment</option><option id="4">satisfying</option><option id="5">supplements</option><option id="6">skate</option><option id="7">smell</option><option id="8">miserable</option><option id="9">cultivating</option><option id="10">satisfactory</option><option id="11">make … through</option><option id="12">sense</option><option id="13">mysterious</option><option id="14">make … up</option><option id="15">self-respect</option></choice><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" weight="1.0"><tip /></question></assessmentItem></section><section title="Section B" type=""><prompt><text type="direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;There are several passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice.</text><text type="p_direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;There are several passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice.</text></prompt><assessmentItem identifier="416D6AB776254136B43DA5079FF51603" baseType="reading" type="readingChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><prompt><text type="guide">Passage One</text><text type="guide">Questions 31 to 35 are based on the following passage.</text>        The estimates of the numbers of home-schooled children vary widely. The U.S. Department of Education estimates there are 250,000 to 350,000 home-schooled children in the country. Home school advocates put the number much higher — at about a million.
        Public schools take a harsh attitude toward home schoolers, perceiving their actions as the ultimate slap in the face for public education and a damaging move for the children. Home schoolers harbor few kind words for public schools, charging shortcomings that range from lack of religious perspective in the curriculum to a herdlike approach to teaching children.
        Yet, as public school officials realize they stand little to gain by remaining hostile to the home school population, and as home schoolers realize they can reap benefits from public schools, these hard lines seem to be softening a bit. 
        Public schools and home schoolers have moved closer to tolerance and, in some cases even cooperation. Says John Marshall, an education official, "we are becoming relatively tolerant of home schoolers. The idea is, let’s give the kids access to public school so they’ll see it’s not as terrible as they’ve been told, and they’ll want to come back." Perhaps, but don’t count on it, say home school advocates. 
        Home schoolers oppose the system because they have strong convictions that their approach to education — whether fueled by religious enthusiasm or the individual child’s interest and natural pace — is the best. "The bulk of home schoolers just want to be left alone." says Enge Cannon, associate director of the National Center for Home Education. She says home schoolers choose that path for a variety of reasons, but religion plays a role 85 percent of the time. 
        Professor Van Galen breaks home schoolers into two groups. Some home schoolers want their children to learn not only traditional subject matter but also "strict religious doctrine (教条) and a conservative political and social perspective. Not incidentally, they also want their children to learn — both intellectually and emotionally — that the family is the most important institution in society." Other home schoolers contend "not so much that the schools teach heresy (异端邪说), but that schools teach whatever they teach inappropriately." Van Galen writes. "These parents are highly independent and strive to take responsibility for their own lives within a society that they define as bureaucratic (官僚主义) and inefficient."</prompt><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>Which of the following statements is true?</prompt><choice><option id="1">Home schoolers engage private teachers to provide additional education for their children.</option><option id="2">Home schoolers don’t go to school but are educated at home by their parents.</option><option id="3">Home schoolers educate their children at home instead of sending them to school.</option><option id="4">Home schoolers advocate combining public education with home schooling.</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>Public schools are softening their position on home schooling because ________.</prompt><choice><option id="1">they want to show their tolerance for different teaching systems</option><option id="2">there isn’t much they can do to change the present situation</option><option id="3">they have so many problems that they cannot offer proper education for all children</option><option id="4">home schooling provides a new variety of education for children</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>Most home schoolers’ opposition to public education stems from their _______.</prompt><choice><option id="1">concern with the cost involved</option><option id="2">worry about the inefficiency of public schools</option><option id="3">devotion to religion</option><option id="4">respect for the interests of individuals</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>From the passage we know that home school advocates think that ________.</prompt><choice><option id="1">home schooling is superior and therefore they will not easily give in</option><option id="2">their increased cooperation with public schools will bring about the improvement of public education</option><option id="3">public schooling is not so bad as has often been said</option><option id="4">their tolerance of public education will attract more kids to public schools</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>It can be concluded from Van Galen’s research that some home schoolers believe that ________.</prompt><choice><option id="1">teachers in public schools are not as responsible as they should be</option><option id="2">public schools take up a herdlike approach to teaching children</option><option id="3">public schools are the source of bureaucracy and inefficiency in modern society</option><option id="4">public schools cannot provide education that is good enough for their children</option></choice><tip /></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="BF9A893FB34944448BA885A96CA5001E" type="readingChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1-8" baseType="reading"><prompt><text type="guide">Passage Two</text><text type="guide">Questions 36 to 40 are based on the following passage.</text><text>        It is well that young men should begin at the beginning and occupy the most subordinate positions. Many of the leading businessmen of Pittsburgh had a serious responsibility thrust upon them at the very threshold of their career. They were introduced to the broom, and spent the first hours of their business lives sweeping out the office. I notice we have janitors and janitresses now in offices, and our men unfortunately miss that beneficial branch of business education. But if by chance the professional sweeper is absent any morning, the boy who has the genius of the future partner in him will not hesitate to try his hand at the broom. It dose not hurt the newest comer to sweep out the office if necessary. I was one of those sweepers myself.
        Assuming that you have all obtained employment and are fairly started, my advice to you is "aim high." Say to yourself, "My place is at the top." Be king in your dreams. And here is the prime condition of success, the great secret: concentrate your energy, thought, and capital exclusively upon the business in which you are engaged. The &lt;i&gt;concerns&lt;/i&gt; which fail are those which have scattered their capital, which means that they have scattered their brains also. "Don't put all your eggs in one basket" is all wrong. I tell you "put all your eggs in one basket, and then watch that basket." Look around you and take notice; men who do that do not often fail. It is easy to watch and carry the one basket. It is trying to carry too many baskets that break most eggs in the country. He who carries three baskets must put one on his head, which is apt to tremble and trip (摔倒) him up.</text></prompt><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>The author will be glad to see a young man ______ the first day he is at work.</prompt><choice><option id="1">trying his hand at a broom</option><option id="2">walking around the office</option><option id="3">reading books</option><option id="4">absent from work</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>The author ______.</prompt><choice><option id="1">started his career by sweeping out the office</option><option id="2">looks down on the janitors and janitresses</option><option id="3">pays respect to the janitors and janitresses</option><option id="4">thinks it unnecessary to have a professional sweeper</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>According to the passage, ______ is an indispensable part of business education.</prompt><choice><option id="1">being a good janitor or janitress</option><option id="2">starting from sweeping in the office</option><option id="3">learning to use the computer</option><option id="4">getting familiar with the Internet</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>______ is essential in your way to success.</prompt><choice><option id="1">Patience</option><option id="2">Concentration</option><option id="3">Perseverance</option><option id="4">Modesty</option></choice><tip /></question><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="2.00"><prompt>In the second paragraph, "concerns" is most close in meaning to ______.</prompt><choice><option id="1">firms</option><option id="2">worries</option><option id="3">businessmen</option><option id="4">deals</option></choice><tip /></question></assessmentItem></section></part></group><group duration="660" navigationMode="nonlinear"><part title="Vocabulary and Structure"><section title="Section A" type=""><prompt><text type="direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;There are a number of incomplete sentences in this part. For each sentence there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Choose the &lt;b&gt;ONE &lt;/b&gt;that best completes the sentence.</text><text type="p_direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt;There are a number of incomplete sentences in this part. For each sentence there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Choose the &lt;b&gt;ONE &lt;/b&gt;that best completes the sentence.</text></prompt><assessmentItem identifier="1A0A39AA85C64853857E83627BE93C05" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>By buying five books every month, I soon _____ a library.</prompt><choice><option id="1">accumulated</option><option id="2">accelerated</option><option id="3">accurate</option><option id="4">accommodated</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="D0D0BF638A1D4E76B6DDDB0C8527FBAD" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>
              &lt;i&gt;King Lear&lt;/i&gt; is one of Shakespeare’s _____. The play ends with the very sad death of Cordelia and Lear.</prompt><choice><option id="1">comedies</option><option id="2">concerts</option><option id="3">cartoons</option><option id="4">tragedies</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="445546DB07AE49149D9B9FB7E7B8CD09" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>It took me six months to _____ the wild horse.</prompt><choice><option id="1">breed</option><option id="2">tame</option><option id="3">cultivate</option><option id="4">tend</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="7587671BDB3F4C71A14D548E9D99CE10" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>The government takes great efforts to balance _____.</prompt><choice><option id="1">expenditure</option><option id="2">outcome</option><option id="3">budget</option><option id="4">asset</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="14DE9F89F73141B7AEEF6071969936D4" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>The battle won with so great a loss of soldiers that it was a(n) _____ defeat.</prompt><choice><option id="1">virtual</option><option id="2">verbal</option><option id="3">superficial</option><option id="4">artificial</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="8F6D936AD09342E9AA69D11BCFE44CF9" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程3" unit="1" unitTo="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>One foolish mistake can _____ you in a good deal of trouble.</prompt><choice><option id="1">release</option><option id="2">involve</option><option id="3">evolve</option><option id="4">empower</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="D8AD44D6FA084401B8F841A365B9B393" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程第三册" unit="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>I would just as soon you _______ this book because I’ve got one already.</prompt><choice><option id="1">not buy</option><option id="2">not buying</option><option id="3">didn’t buy</option><option id="4">having not bought</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="D962376F49774D49B4A8AEA9347E6AFF" baseType="simpleChoice" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程第三册" unit="1"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>Our company recruited a new manager to ________ this important project.</prompt><choice><option id="1">see that</option><option id="2">under see</option><option id="3">oversee</option><option id="4">over see</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="F0AC2AF0BF96488489C4231D83FCD356" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1-8" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>All the pupils _____ straight when the teacher came into the classroom.</prompt><choice><option id="1">sat up</option><option id="2">dined out</option><option id="3">cashed in</option><option id="4">passed for</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="C74E8B59DBE64541A653C9BB5F07402F" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1-8" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>Rest assured that your friendship will be _____ with sympathy and kindness.</prompt><choice><option id="1">appreciated</option><option id="2">forged</option><option id="3">repaid</option><option id="4">imposed</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="833EC37D10974964A4D3D1F545523363" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1-8" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>Language not only depends on its culture, but _____ structures reality for this culture.</prompt><choice><option id="1">in particular</option><option id="2">in theory</option><option id="3">in addition</option><option id="4">in turn</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="C92BC609FD054A35846FE0CE2BB036F1" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1-8" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>Economic and trade cooperation between the two countries, which has been built on a consolidated foundation, still has _____ for further development and diversification.</prompt><choice><option id="1">evolution</option><option id="2">compromise</option><option id="3">contentment</option><option id="4">potential</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="DD9207ADF632430CAB2C74354C5B6F7C" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>The attack on our nation is also an attack on the ideals that make us a nation. Our deepest national ______ is that every life is precious, because every life is the gift of a creator who intended us to live in liberty and equality.</prompt><choice><option id="1">requirement</option><option id="2">blessing</option><option id="3">commitment</option><option id="4">conviction</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="0DE22E46A8EF4987B79488B10B3CEED3" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>It's exhausting ______ from Suzhou to Shanghai every day.</prompt><choice><option id="1">crisscrossing</option><option id="2">departing</option><option id="3">prying</option><option id="4">commuting</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="7726678917794F86B25A5D56F3ECEF77" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>If the work _________ completed by the end of this year is delayed, the construction company will be fined.</prompt><choice><option id="1">being</option><option id="2">to be</option><option id="3">will be</option><option id="4">has been</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="7A74C2AEE6344BD8B96E042F13B00A78" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>Who __________ has read Shakespeare's great plays can forget their fascination?</prompt><choice><option id="1">that</option><option id="2">which</option><option id="3">who</option><option id="4">ever</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="6AEAD8E986E541AFBC197FE47D1A7AA7" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>The dressing-table was bare, _________ a pair of ivory hair brushes.</prompt><choice><option id="1">in addition to</option><option id="2">except</option><option id="3">except for</option><option id="4">besides</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="6C0BFF91F9B149C88DA745258ECCECE6" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>Peter complained to the owner of the book store that there were some pages _________ in the dictionary.</prompt><choice><option id="1">losing</option><option id="2">missing</option><option id="3">dropping</option><option id="4">falling</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="C0D20E5E44C7413E83AEB92D1C306E94" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>What she told me about the affair simply doesn't make any ________.</prompt><choice><option id="1">idea</option><option id="2">sense</option><option id="3">meaning</option><option id="4">significance</option></choice></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="E6E47CDEF4E24392AF8C2C52447894D6" type="vocabularyStructureChoice" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleChoice"><question type="choice" strict="true" shuffle="true" weight="1.0"><prompt>Why can't you do this small _________ for me? I've helped you often enough in the past.</prompt><choice><option id="1">demand</option><option id="2">request</option><option id="3">favor</option><option id="4">requirement</option></choice></question></assessmentItem></section></part></group><group duration="600" navigationMode="nonlinear"><part title="Translation"><section title="Section A" type=""><prompt><text type="direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt; Translate the following sentences into English (with the given words or phrases).</text><text type="p_direction">
            &lt;b&gt;Directions: &lt;/b&gt; Translate the following sentences into English (with the given words or phrases).</text></prompt><assessmentItem identifier="7C416D7945A04E8AB9F8A77075B1CFFD" baseType="simpleCloze" type="sentenceTranslation" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程第三册" unit="1"><question type="text" length="66" strict="false" weight="4.00"><prompt>我父亲有时候做点兼职来添补他的收入。
<tag type="text" /></prompt></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="ECCB0A91079444C08199E99E98C6C105" baseType="simpleCloze" type="sentenceTranslation" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程第三册" unit="1"><question type="text" length="57" strict="false" weight="4.00"><prompt>我怀疑我的手表出了问题。
<tag type="text" /></prompt></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="3EA30B0965164EC286AF2B0901D18052" baseType="simpleCloze" type="sentenceTranslation" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程第三册" unit="1"><question type="text" length="56" strict="false" weight="4.00"><prompt>在论文中请用例子来证明你的观点。
<tag type="text" /></prompt></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="4D8C876279274F3D8BE51EABBEC977BC" type="sentenceTranslation" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleCloze"><question type="text" length="113" strict="false" weight="4.00"><prompt>我们不是因为想挣钱才移居此地，我们来此居住是为了提高生活质量。
<tag type="text" /></prompt></question></assessmentItem><assessmentItem identifier="ED9B1E22F32E47BBA3089ABF0F45D775" type="sentenceTranslation" level="3" course="全新版大学英语（第二版）综合教程试题第三册" unit="1" baseType="simpleCloze"><question type="text" length="100" strict="false" weight="4.00"><prompt>追求艺术上的完美是他毕生的事业，虽然在这个世界上，“完美”并不存在。
<tag type="text" /></prompt></question></assessmentItem></section></part></group></paper>